https://www.ipa-usa.org/privacy.aspx

International Police Association (IPA)
Search »
Print Page   |   Contact Us   |   Sign In   |   JOIN IPA!
International Police Association
Home
About the IPAAdvertising Media KitPromo MovieYou Tube MoviesMission/Vision/Value StatementsIPA History
Special Interest
Defensive TacticsPolice CollectorsBicycle TouringAero ClubHobbiesHunting & FishingRadio ClubRVersTravel InternationalTravel USWine Lovers
Regions 1-9
Region 1Region 2Region 4Region 5Region 6Region 8Region 9
Regions 10-19
Region 10Region 11Region 12Region 13Region 14Region 15Region 16Region 17Region 19
Regions 20-29
Region 20Region 21Region 22Region 23Region 24Region 25Region 26Region 27Region 29
Privacy Policy and Use of Cookies
At YourMembership.com we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not rent or resell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. The information we collect is used to provide services to our clients and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read this complete privacy statement.
YourMembership.com, Inc. is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-YourMembership.com websites to which this Site or any other YourMembership.com website may link. Also, YourMembership.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of its Clients or users of its Client websites. You should review any additional privacy policy and terms of use agreements of the entity from whose website you clicked-through before using the site.
Please note that the practices of YourMembership.com, Inc., its affiliates, and agents ("YM"), with respect to data collected and used by YM in connection with this website and all other YM affiliated websites, and its affiliates with links to this policy (collectively, the "Site") and YM services available or enabled via the Site ("Services"), are governed by this online privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") as amended from time to time, and not the privacy policy in effect at the time the data was collected. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and the Services enabled by the Site and follow the procedure described in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences". This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities, websites other than the Site, or any products or services not available or enabled via the Site. Notwithstanding the foregoing, to the extent that any terms of the Privacy Policy conflict with the terms of an existing written (including electronic) agreement between you and the website from which this Policy is linked, this Policy shall take precedence as it relate to the practices of YM.
U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework
YourMembership.com complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. YourMembership.com has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view YourMembership.com's certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/
YourMembership.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU [and EU-Swiss] Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by YourMembership.com, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.
If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact:
YourMembership.com, Inc.
Attn: Privacy Officer
300 First Avenue South, #300
St. Petersburg, FL 33701
USA
If you do not receive acknowledgment of your compliant or your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by YourMembership.com, you should then contact:
Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.
4200 Wilson Boulevard, Suite 800
Arlington, VA 22203
Web: bbb.org
Email: eusafeharbor@council.bbb.org
Entities Collecting Personal Information
Personal information on this site is collected on behalf of the entity from whose web page you clicked-through and who is responsible for this site content and data. Please contact the organization responsible regarding collection questions and data privacy.
The site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided otherwise, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.
Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Profile Information, this may be accomplished by linking to your account at "Edit My Profile", where you can view and make changes to your personal information. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications) by writing the entity at their specified address within their contact information page on the site from which you have clicked.
Personal information submitted through this Site or in connection with the Site that is not Profile Information or is not accessible online. To access and/or correct such information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications), you may write the entity of contact them via their online contact form. In your correspondence, please detail the location on this Site or otherwise where you provided your personal information. You may expect a response within 30 days. For information submitted in connection with Products and Services, you may also follow instructions included or referenced within such Product and Service to access or correct the information.
Collection of Personal Information
As a visitor to this site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online or hosted Services, the Site may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting a form. It is optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, the Site may ask that you provide personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including postal code), country of residence, e-mail address, employer, title, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When participating in electronic commerce via the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that is asked of you may be mandatory and some may be voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. Similarly, if you wish to delete your information (pursuant to the mechanism set forth in "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences") that is mandatory, you will no longer be able to engage in a particular activity.
When you use the site and the Products and Services, the site may also collect certain information about your computer to facilitate and evaluate your use of the site and the Products and Services. For example, the site may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, referring or exit webpages, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. The Site also uses such information to measure traffic patterns on the Site and usage of the YM Services. YM does not match such information with any other information held by YM unless we have your consent.
By using this site, you agree and acknowledge that personal information collected through the Site or in connection with the services provided may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which YM maintains offices, including the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted third parties. Such third parties are bound by contract with YM not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. One instance where this could occur is in conjunction with framed pages in which the URL for the pages is not visible, and the pages are hosted for YM by such third parties. For example, on the sign up pages for some newsletters, the pages may be hosted by a third party vendor, but appear to be pages operated by YM and are governed by the YM privacy policy.
Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a third party provider's website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on that site, and personal information that you provide while on this Site will be subject to this Privacy Policy.
How Your Personal Information is Used
YM collects your information in order to record, support and facilitate your participation on the site from which this policy is linked. If you subscribe to or register on the site, for example, the information is used provide access to the website and other benefits that may be made available to registered users. Your personal information is also used to track your website preferences and keep you informed within the community unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law.
YM may collect information about the use of the Services and the site, such as the number of downloads, types of Services used, how many users we receive daily, and the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually.
YM may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for improving the Site and Services, providing more relevant experiences to our clients and for statistical analysis.
Use of Cookies
When someone visits this site, standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns are collected. This is done to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is collected in a manner in which it does not identify anyone. No attempts are made to find out the identities of those visiting this site. No data gathered from this site is associated to/with any personally identifying information from any source. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings.
Google Analytics cookies may be used on this site. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use this site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors come to the site from, browsing patterns on this site, and the pages they visited.
Please note that YM is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-YM websites to which this site or any other YM website may link. Also, YM is not responsible for the privacy practices of its Clients or users of its Client websites. You should review the additional privacy policy of the Client site before using the site and contact the organization should you have questions regarding their policies.
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't registered yet?
Latest News
more
8/15/2020Scholarship Club Winners
4/26/2013PLEASE READ!
Association Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
